User Interface, experience and Brand Designer



Tel: (+47)455 07 088 predrage@pm.me

Predrag has over 18 years of work experience in design and web development. Open and creative approach helps him design inclusive and accessible product and service experience that fits seamlessly into people's lives. App interface design and solution development beside webdesign are his main areas of expertise and professional interest.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Designer, Dekode, Oslo — 2022 — now

Specialized for concept design, identity and Webside. Worked for the biggest NGO in Norway, contributed in winning competitions.

Senior Product Designer, Aller Media, Oslo — 2021—2022

Product designer for Aller Digital team, developing digital services, video platform and UX design.

Senior Interactive Designer, Sixty, Bergen — 2018—2021

User Experience and Interface design for sport applications and new generation of interactive TV graphics. Developing technologies that enable user interactivity within digital broadcast. Had an opportunity to work with major global brands from US to Asia (more under references page 2).

Product Designer, FrontEnd, Intutor Group, Bergen -2012-2018

Developed and worked on some of the biggest systems in Norway; Developing systems from scratch, system for traffic schools and students;

Designer, Consultant, Shanghai, China — 2011,2012

"Apollo BC", ANS-architects and Event Marketing Agency. Worked with wine distributers on promotions of different wine regions for the Chinese market.

Vino & Fino Magazine — 2012

Designer, Developer, Human Vision web studio, Serbia — **2007-2011** Designer and Developer, innovation in e-commerce and social networking.

Co-founder, Designer for Magazine "Gurman Press" — **2002-2006** Entrepreneurship with friends/ partners. Publishing magazines.

Designer at "Tuck Video" Cine and Video Production — **2002-2003** Official distributor for Serbia Warner Bros, Sony Pictures...

Don't hesitate to say hello and inform me about your ideas for collaborations.

11010331

Predrag is a Norwegian citizen, living in Bergen, was born in Serbia 1978



Portfolio pktch.github.io/design

EDUCATION

School of commerce "JezdimirLovic" Belgrade (IV degree); MCP - Microsoft Certificated Professional - Network Infrastructure Administrator; Certificated ProfessionalSommelier; W3School certificate in CSS

SKILLS

User Interface and Experience Design

In close collaboration with clients, helping them to improve relation with customer base. Fresh eyes, open and creative approach help designing inclusive and accessible product or service experience that fits seamlessly into people's lives.

FrontEnd Development

In phase of project development, Predrag can help team with FrontEnd Development. Advanced HTML/CSS skills, working in popular frameworks and minimalJS.

PROJECT REFERENCES

ANSA - Identity and Website design; Røde Kors - Webshop; SOS Barnebyer -Competition, 1stprize (role design); ABBL - webdesign; Gjensidigestiftelsen - brand identity works and web design. **Naturvenforbundet** - webdesign; **Promon**- identity and webdesign; **Aller** - video platform; **Bundesliga** - User Interface & Experience research for mobile device fort the live broadcast, conference-simultaneous game play watching (Sixty, 2018); PremierLeague -User Interface & Experience study for mobile experience of a live broadcast (Sixty 2019); Allsvenskan - Competition, 1stprize for design. Broadcast graphics for TV and mobile experience design. (Sixty 2020); Tencent -Interactive broadcast experience design and graphics for mobile (Sixty 2020); **VICE** - Case study-how to incorporate eShop widget on mobile whilewatching program (Sixty 2019); CBS - Interactive infographics, Q&A interface, mobile TV experience design (Sixty 2019); BonaMea - User Interface & Experience, Branding, website. (Intutor, 2016); MyKid - User Interface & Experience, Branding, website. (Intutor, 2014)... Trafikkskoleportalen (today's TABS) Product design for administration, booking system that became choice of over 80% traffic schools in Norway.

CONTACT REFERENCES

Christopher Kvarme, Team lead for Aller apps, tel: +4791160618 Asle Birkeland fmr Design VP, co-founder Sixty, tel: +4795215 Bjarte Århus CEO Intutor AS, tel: +4790181141